mylescars.com 2019-12-14

# Myles: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") discloses the privacy practices for Myles Automotive Technologies Private Limited ("Myles") website ("website"). Myles places paramount importance on maintaining the privacy of its customers'("User") personal information under the applicable laws in India.  
Please read this Policy carefully by accessing or using our website. The User hereby acknowledges that he has read, understood, and agrees to be bound to all the terms of this Policy and our website's terms of use before the User proceeds.  

**Personal Information- What personal information is collected from the user?**

Myles collects and uses relevant personal information of User in order to provide services. The following personal information ("information") is collected from the User and shall include ,though not limited to, the User's street address, name, contact telephone number; vehicle preference; company name and employee accounts with Myles; Reservations and Rental details including dates, times and places of vehicle hire; ; online feedback surveys; electronic records/databases of all rental agreements;

**How this information will be used by the company?**

The collection of information shall depend upon on the User's use of Myles's services. Myles may collect information directly from the User by mobile devices, portable devices (Tablet) /telephone/fax/email/over the counter/filling an enrollment form or through an internet based service.  
The User may choose not to provide some information but this may prevent Myles from providing the standard of services that is normally expected. The User by proceeding with the usage/access of the website/application of the Myles explicitly grants his/her consent to such usage of the data by the Myles.   
Myles protects information by keeping up to date with techniques and processes meeting current industry standards ensuring that information are kept secure and confidential. Only employees of Myles and those who perform services on their behalf shall be authorized to handle & have access to the information.  
Myles shall make best possible endeavors to use the data of the Users for rendering standard services only by sharing it with third party companies. Myles will be careful in the management of information of Users and also has measures in place to ensure that collected information is protected and not accessed inappropriately. Myles makes every effort to ensure that information of User is accurate and updated and requires User to verify their identity for security purposes before replying to any requests.   
Any User who has an objection to such usage must not proceed with the usage/access of the website/application of Myles.  
The User who has already shared his/her personal data may raise the demand to Myles for removal of his/her data at registered office address mentioned below.  
Registered office address is 9th Floor, Videocon Tower, E1 Block, Jhandewalan Extension, New Delhi, Central Delhi, Delhi, India – 110055.

**How the company transfers data to third party companies?**

Myles does not submit information to third parties except in the following cases:  

Receive permission of the User. On outsourcing activities, wherein Myles ensures that strict management of the information is enforced through a separately executed non-disclosure agreement. Disclosure of information in order to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Policy, our website terms of use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others. On sharing of information in a Business Transfer i.e. in case of a merger with, or be acquired by another company. In good faith so as to protect the property of Myles, or to protect the safety of employees and their families.

Any information provided to or gathered by this website is controlled primarily by Myles, whose registered office address is 9th Floor, Videocon Tower, E1 Block, Jhandewalan Extension, New Delhi, Central Delhi, Delhi, India – 110055.  

**Cookies**

Myles stores cookies on the User's computer in order to facilitate and customize the experience with the Website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. Cookies are used to save time while using the website, tracking and targeting User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Myles may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on the Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on the User's computer. This Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. The User may be able to modify the browser settings to decline cookies. The User notes that on modifications of cookies, some parts of the website may not work properly.

**Security**

The access is through user Id and password. The storage of information of the User is in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. As transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, Myles shall strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect User's information. Myles hereby states that it does not guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the website, and is not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

**Links to other sites**

The Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Myles. The User needs to be aware that Myles shall not be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Therefore Myles encourages the User to be aware on leaving the website and read the privacy statements of each and every other site that collects information. This Policy applies only to information collected by this website.

**How to edit this information or log out?**

The access to users account is through user ID login and passwords and Myles persuades that the user promptly updates information if it changes in order to help Myles keep the information and up to date. The access would be withdrawn if such facility is not to be continued.  
However, Myles keeps track of past transactions, therefore the User cannot delete information or opt-out of information associated with past transactions on the website.

**Changes or Modifications to the Policy**

The changes made herein to the Policy shall be made without prior notice under the heading "Privacy Policy" section of the Website. The revised Policy is effective immediately when posted on the website. The User's continued use of the website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute the User's acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Policy.   

**Disclaimer**

Every effort has been made to ensure that the information on this site is correct and up to date, however, Myles does not provide any warranty as to the completeness or accuracy of the information and, subject to applicable laws, does not accept any liability for damages of any kind resulting from the access or use of this website and its contents. All information on this site is protected by copyright and other intellectual property rights. No images, text or other content from this site may be distributed or reproduced without prior written approval from Myles.

The images used in the website are displayed for informational purposes only. We do not intend to violate Intellectual Property Rights of the respective models & brands. We assume no responsibility for any errors or omissions for these images as they are used for representational purposes only. We make no commitment to update the information contained herein. We expressly disclaim any, representations or warranties, express or implied, regarding the images, including, without limitation, any implied warranties and their merchantability. We expressly disclaim any, warranties, express or implied, regarding the correctness, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, and reliability of the text, graphics, links to other sites and any other items accessed from or via this Website or the Internet, or that the services will be uninterrupted, error-free or free of viruses or other harmful components.

Under no circumstances, we or any of our affiliates, or any of the respective partners, officers, directors, employees, agents or representatives be liable or be implicated for any damages, whether direct, indirect, special or consequential damages for lost revenues, lost profits, or otherwise, arising from or in connection with this Website, the materials contained herein, or the Internet generally.

All materials contained in this Website are protected by copyright laws, and may not be reproduced, republished, distributed, transmitted, displayed, broadcast or otherwise exploited in any manner without the express prior written permission from us.

By proceeding with the access or usage to our website, you expressly agree by such access or usage that you have read and understood all the terms & conditions set herewith and all the provisions mentioned on our website and that you have agreed to be bound by the terms set by us. By access or usage of our website, you are expressly waiving off your right to claim damages and reliefs from/against us from respective Courts/Forums.

**Contact Us**
